1. callTestCase(findTestCase("Modular Component/FIRST TC Open Connect (Delay 10s)"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. maximizeWindow()
9. navigateToUrl(TEST)
13. delay(5)
5. callTestCase(findTestCase("Modular Component/Click - My record (Delay 10s)"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. delay(10)
5. click(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Link - Objects/Link - Dashboard - My record"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
9. delay(10, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
9. click(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Link - Objects/Link - My record - ERNI Information"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
13. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
19. "My record" tab will not be available in viewport if "ERNI Information" is at the top-most of viewport.
23. verifyElementVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - ERNI Information"), 0)
29. Click "Contact Information"
33. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
39. ERNI Information portion will not be available in viewport if Contact Information" is at the top-most of viewport.
43. verifyElementVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Contact information"), 0)
49. Click "Career Summary"
53. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
57. verifyElementNotVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Contact information"), 1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
61. verifyElementVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Career Summary"), 0)
67. Click "Roles"
71. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
75. verifyElementNotVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Career Summary"), 1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
79. verifyElementVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Roles"), 0)
85. Click "Widgets"
89. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
93. verifyElementNotVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Roles"), 1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
97. verifyElementVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Widgets"), 0)
103. Click "Skills Overview"
107. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
111. verifyElementNotVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Widgets"), 1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
115. verifyElementVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Skills Overview"), 0)
121. Click "ERNI Trainings"
125. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
129. verifyElementNotVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Skills Overview"), 1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
133. verifyElementVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - ERNI Trainings"), 0)
139. Click "Education"
143. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
147. verifyElementNotVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - ERNI Trainings"), 1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
151. verifyElementVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Education"), 0)
157. Click "Experience"
161. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
165. verifyElementNotVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Education"), 1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
169. verifyElementInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Experience"), 0)
175. Click "Projects"
179. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
183. verifyElementNotVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Experience"), 1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
187. verifyElementVisibleInViewport(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - My record/Viewport - Objects/Viewport - My record - Projects"), 0)