1. callTestCase(findTestCase("Modular Component/FIRST TC Open Connect (Delay 10s)"), ["URL":"https://connect-test.erninet.ch/3#Home"], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. maximizeWindow()
9. navigateToUrl(TEST)
13. delay(5)
5. callTestCase(findTestCase("Modular Component/Click - People Search (Delay 10s)"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. delay(10)
5. click(findTestObject("Smoke Test/People - People Search/Link - Objects/Link - Dashboard - People Search"))
9. delay(10)
11. Verify "People Search" Tab is Visible
17. Verify "Enity Dropdown" is Visible
23. Verify "Search Field" is Visible
29. Verify "Filter" dropdown is Visible
35. Verify "Show Columns" Dropdown is Visible
41. Verify "Export" Button is Visible
47. Verify Main Table is Visible
53. Verify ERNI Logo is Visible